好吧 钱德 摩妮卡 只剩一个香蕉坚果松饼了
Okay, Chandler, Mon, there's only one banana-nut muffin left.
我先说要的
I ordered mine first.
是啊 但是我比较快
Yeah, but I'm so much faster.
给我
Give it to me.
不要
No.
给我
Give it to me.
好吧 你可以拿去
Okay, you can have it.
好吧 享受你的咖啡吧
There you go. Enjoy your coffee.
我来这儿时就已经在桌上了
That was there when I got here.
嘿 你们绝对猜不到 谁要来纽约
Hey, you guys, you will never guess who's coming to New York.
快点 菲比 在他咽下去之前快告诉我们
Quick Phoebe tell us before he swallows.
好 是雷恩 和我约过会 在海军服役的那个
OK Ryan, that guy I went out with who's in the Navy.
你和在海军服役的人约会?
You went out with a guy in the Navy?
是啊 我在华盛顿广场公园弹吉他时遇到他
Yeah. I met him while playing guitar in the park.
雷恩给我太妃糖 因为他没有零钱
Ryan threw in saltwater taffy because he didn't have change.
嘿 所以你就写了《太妃糖人》?
Hey, is that when you wrote 'SaltwaterTaffyMan'?
不是
No. Heh.
不是 他是我的潜艇人 他每两年就会出水一次
No.he's my submarine guy. He resurfaces, like, every couple years...
然后我们就会一起度过最棒的三天
and we have the most amazing three days together
只不过这一次 他会来两个星期
Only this time,he's coming for two weeks.
整整两个星期 也就是耶
Two whole weeks, which meansyay."
等等 这家伙一潜到水底下 就是两年?
So wait, this guy goes down for like, two years at a time?
这就是舔我的松饼的代价
That'll teach you to lick my muffin.
嗨
Hi.
哦 糟糕 发生了什么事?
Oh, no. What happened?
我刚才和卡萝通话 小班得了水痘
I just spoke to Carol. Ben's got the chickenpox.
哦 不是真的吧
Oh, no.You're kidding.
是啊 所以如果你还没有得过 你很可能会得
Yeah, so if you haven't had it, chances are you're gonna get it.
好吧 我已经得过了      是啊 我得过了
Well,I've had it.        Yeah I've had it.
得过了      得过了
Had it.        Had it.
我从来没有得过 我觉得好孤单 哦 你看
I've never had it. I feel so left out. Oh look.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第23集
出水痘 The One With the Chicken Pox
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：Phoebe
亲爱的 你又铺好床了
Honey, you made the bed again.
我告诉你 你不必这么做 这又不是营地
I told you, you don't have to do that. This isn't camp.
所以我猜昨晚偷内裤 是完全不必要的了
Oh. Then I guess the panty raid last night was totally uncalled for.
好吧 我要去冲个澡
Okay, I am going to take a shower.
今天我会唱吉姆克罗齐的《李洛伊布朗》
And today I will be singing Jim Croces"LeroyBrown."
摩妮卡?
Monica?
嘿 摩妮卡 我有一个问题
Hey, Mon, I have a question.
李洛伊是整个镇最坏的人
Is Leroy the baddest man in the whole damn town...
还是整个镇最胖的人?
...or the fattest man in the whole damn town?
最坏的 否则这首歌 就会是《肥肥李洛伊布朗》
The baddest. Otherwise, the song would be'Fat,Fat LeroyBrown.'
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我只是在等待着你 亲爱的
I'm just waiting for you, sweetie.
你在重铺床?
Are you remaking the bed?
对不起 对不起 你知道吗? 你弄的根本没问题
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You know what? The way you did it. It was just fine.
那你重铺是因为...?
Then you're redoing it because...?
如果我告诉你 你会认为我疯了
If I tell you, you'll think I'm crazy.
反正已经无可避免
You're pretty much running that risk either way.
好吧 你看...
Okay. You see...
棉被的标签不该是在左上角
the duvet tag shouldn't be at the top left corner...
应该是在右下角
it should be at the bottom right corner.
嗯 这不是太疯狂啊
Uh-huh. Well,that's not so crazy.
我只是用简单的方法解释给你听
I'm just easing you in.
好的
Ha. All right.
好 你有看到这些小花朵吗?
All right, you see these little flower blossoms?
它们应该朝上 不是朝下
They should be facing up, not down...
因为...床头应该是太阳出来的地方
because, well, the head of the bed is where the sun would be.
你不爱我了 对吧?
You don't love me anymore, do you?
其实 如果可能的话 我更爱你
Actually, if it's possible, I love you more.
真的吗?
Really?
好吧 那么 来吧
Wow. Well, then, come on.
我想让你看如何 把卫生纸折成三角形
I wanna show you how to fold the toilet paper into a point.
乔伊 如果你需要工作...
Joey, if you need something to hold you over
我这里就可以给你一份工作 当入门处理员
I can get you a job right here as an entry-level processor.
那样的工作不用经验吗?
Don't you need experience for a job like that?
并不是很难学
It's not that hard to learn.
当人发现你不知道你在做什么时...
And as for people realizing you don't know what you're doing,
嘿 你是演员耶
hey, you're an actor.
就演得像个处理员 人们就会认为你是一位处理员
Act like a processor, people will think you're a processor.
嘿 钱德 这是今天上午的预测
Hey, Chandler. Here's this morning's projections.
嘿 史考特亚历山大 谢谢 这是乔伊崔比亚尼
Hey, thanks. Scott Alexander, Joey Tribbiani.
嘿      嘿
Hey        Hey.
乔伊是一位处理员
Joey is a, uh, fellow processor.
不是开玩笑吧?
No kidding?
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
我处理人们要处理的东西 我是他们要找的人
I process. People want the processing, I'm the one they call.
你在哪儿工作?      好吧 我现在待业中
Where do you work?        Uh. well, right now I'm in between things.
你知道是怎么回事 有一天 你在处理 第二天...
You know how it is. One day you're processing, the next day...
你没有那么多... 可处理了
...you're not so much processing anymore.
我正跟乔伊讲佛莱许曼小组的职缺的事呢
I was telling Joey about the opening in Fleischman's group.
佛莱许曼小组
Fleischman's group.
不管你做什么 不要碰他的三明治
Whatever you do, don't touch his sandwiches.
你们处理员都是笨蛋吗?
Are all you processors dorks?
这口红你涂起来很美
Ugh. This lipstick looks just great on you.
你看起来很美 亲爱的 真的
You look fabulous, honey. You really do.
是啊 你确定吗?真的吗?
Yeah, are you sure? Really?
看 你看起来很漂亮 拜托 把灯光调暗
See, you look beautiful. For God sakes, dim the lights.
我好吓人啊
I'm hideous.
不会有问题的
It's gonna be okay.
雷恩在水底下很久
Ryan's been underwater
你的屁股上没有长牡蛎他就已经很开心了
he's just gonna be so glad that you don't have barnacles on your butt.
进来
Come in.
嘿 宝贝 我回来了
Hey, baby, I'm back.
嘿 雷恩 你好吗?
Hey, Ryan. What's up?
这是怎么回事?
What's going on?
不...你必须保持距离 我长了痘痘
No, no. You have to stay back. I have the pox.
水痘还是天花?
Chicken or small?
是水痘 真是讽刺 因为我是素食主义者
Chicken, which is so ironic considering I'm a vegetarian.
为什么你不躺在家里休息?
Why aren't you at home in bed?
因为我祖母从未得过水痘
My grandmother's never had chicken pox.
拜托 拜托 告诉我你得过
Please, please, tell me you have...
因为...哦 我的天 我忘了你有多么可爱
...because oh, my God, I forgot how cute you are.
对不起 我从来没有得过      噢 噢
I'm sorry, I never had them.        Oh. oh!
如果我有一个愿望 我会组装一台 时间机器
If I had one wish,it'd be to build a time machine,
回到我七岁时
go back to when I was 7
当吉米豪瑟得水痘时...
when Jimmy Hauser had chicken pox...
我会抓住那小子 用他抹遍我的脸
I would grab that kid and rub him all over my face.
是啊 或者 你知道 你可以希望我现在没有得水痘
Yeah, or, you know, you could just wish that I didn't have them now.
求你了 我可以看看你的脸吗?
Can I please see your face?
不要 你不会想看到长满痘痘的脸的
No. You don't wanna see a face covered with pox.
就算你的脸上全是鲑鱼 我也不会在意
Your face could be covered with lox, I wouldn't care.
而且你讨厌鱼 噢
And you hate fish. Oh.
真贴心 好吧
So sweet. All right.
好吧 你可以看
Okay, all right. You can see.
这就是我
This, ahem, is me.
对不起
Sorry.
我很可怕
I am scary.
对不起 是闪电...
Sorry, the lightning
闪电是不幸的巧合
Lightning was an unfortunate coincidence.
你看起来很可爱
You look lovely. Lovely.
我讨厌这样
I hate this.
我告诉你 我为我们计划了 最棒的两周
I tell you, I had the most amazing two weeks planned for us.
在我脑海里 我们比现在这样亲近多了
And almost everything I had in mind, we had to be a lot closer than this.
菲比 我花了将近八个月时间
Phoebe, l've spent the last eight months
与男人们在钢管中生活
in a steel tube with men...
一直都在想像这个时刻
thinking about this moment.
我不会让一堆...
I am not gonna let a bunch...
会发痒的斑点挡在我们之间
of itchy spots stand between us.
好吧 这是我得过最浪漫的病了
Okay. This is the most romantic disease I've ever had.
嘿      嘿 第一天过得如何?
Hey.        Hey.How's the first day going?
相当不错 就像你说的那样
Pretty good.It's like you said.
大部分只是把号码从一列填到另一列
It's mostly just putting numbers from one column into another column.
对啊 就是这样
Well, there you go.
嘿 大家都好友善
Hey, and everybody's so nice.
我刚才在和一位红头发叫珍妮的女士畅谈
I just had a good talk with that lady with the red hair, Jeannie.
珍妮? 东岸开发部门的主管 珍妮?
Jeannie? The head of East Coast Operations, Jeannie?
是啊 原来我们的孩子上同一所学校
Yeah. Turns out our kids go to the same school.
是啊 世界真小 对吧?
Yeah. Small world, huh?
世界真怪
Weird world.
你的孩子?      我想我的角色应该有孩子
Your kids?        l figure my character has kids.
你知道 你这句话我一个字也没听懂吧?
You know, there isn't a part of that sentence that I don't need explained.
嗯 知道吗 当你在演戏时 你需要思考这样的东西
Well, see, when you're acting, you need to think about stuff like that.
我的角色 处理员约瑟夫...
My character Joseph the processing guy...
有两个小女儿 爱什莉和布莉塔妮
has two little girls, Ashley and Brittany.
爱什莉重复布莉塔妮所做的一切
Ashley copies everything Brittany does.
嗯 无形的孩子 有时是会这样
Oh. Well, invisible kids can be that way sometimes.
没错 你知道吗 约瑟夫和他的妻子
Yeah, yeah. You know, Joseph and his wife,
凯伦在考虑生第三个孩子
Karen, are thinking of having a third kid.
你知道吗?
You know what?
刚刚生了
Just did.
真的 哇 你一定是有一些非常强而有力的想像精子
Really, wow.That's some pretty powerful imaginary sperm you must have there.
你知道是什么能使痒痒更糟糕吗?
You know what makes the itching even worse?
你不停谈论它吗?
That you don't stop talking about it?
好吧      我们玩就好了 好吗?
Fine.        Let's just play, okay?
好
Good, okay.
来吧 双六
Here we go, double sixes.
来吧...
Here we go...
来吧
Here we go.
来吧 准备掷骰子了
Come to Mama. Just getting ready to roll the dice.
你在做什么? 你在抓痒吗?
What are you doing? Are you scratching?
没有 我这是在祈求好运 好吗?
No. This is what I do for luck, okay?
你在抓痒
You're scratching.
给我骰子      不要
Give me the dice.        No.
给我骰子      不要 拿去
Give me the dice.        No. Here. There.
你看 双六
Look. double sixes.
我们不能抓痒 你知道的 我们不能 会有疤痕
We can't scratch. You know we can't. Well scar.
我没办法不想 好难喔
I can't stop thinking about it. It's just so hard.
我只想拿起这些房子 摩擦我每一寸皮肤
I just wanna grab these houses and rub them all over my body.
不行      给我
No. No.        Give it.
给我
Come on.
你知道你想要 你知道你也想要 来吧
You know you want it. You know you want it too. Come on.
我们都反叛一次 感觉会很棒的
Let's just be bad.It'll feel so good.
哦 来吧 来吧
Oh, come on. Come on.
哦 上帝 帮助我
Uh-huh.        Oh, God, help me.
好啊?      是啊
Uh-huh. Good, huh?        Yeah.
哦 是的      好 可以了 现在你抓我
Oh, yeah.        Okay, good. Now do me.
抓我的背 哦 来吧 用力一点
Do my back. Oh, come on. Harder.
就这样
There you go.
不要动      为什么?
Don't move.        Why?
不要动      你在...?
Don't move.        What are you...?
停下 现在就停下
Aah! Stop that. Stop that right now.
你知道吗 菲比 我想过你可能会这样
You know, I might've expected this of you, Phoebe.
但是 雷恩 你是一个军人耶
But, Ryan, you're a military man.
你和米尔顿一定要到我们船上来玩
You and Milton have to join us on the boat.
凯伦会准备午餐
Karen will pack a lunch,
你带孩子来 这一天我们会玩得很开心
you bring the kids. We'll make a day of it.
噢 听起来很棒 我们得订一个时间
Oh, that sounds lovely. We're gonna have to set that up.
噢 我得回去了 希望宝宝感觉好点了
Oh, I better get back. Hope the baby feels better.
噢 谢谢 谢谢
Oh, thanks. Thanks.
再见 珍妮      再见 约瑟夫
Bye-bye, Jeannie.        Bye-bye, Joseph.
好假的一个人
What a phony.
好了 我相信当她走下
Well,I'm sure you'll teach her a lesson
空无一物的码头时她就知道教训了
when she steps off the dock onto nothing.
嘿 道格拉斯先生      老板
Hey, Mr. Douglas.        Sir.
听着 宾 我收到了你的备忘录
Uh, listen, Bing, I got your memo.
我们要到下周五才看得到报告?
So we're not gonna see the report until next Friday?
我这组的人想与家人共度周末的节日
Well, the people in my group want to spend the holiday with family.
我也是有家的人 但我还是会在这儿的
I have a family. I'm gonna be here.
是啊 宾 那是怎么一回事呢?
Yeah, Bing. What's that about?
是要让我的人休息一下 知道吗 振奋一下士气
It's about cutting my people a little slack, you know, for morale.
如果你想看粗略的数字 我星期三前就可以给你
If you wanna see some rough numbers, I can get them to you by Wednesday.
粗略数字?
Rough numbers?
这家公司可不是用粗略数字建立的
This company was not built on rough numbers.
对吧 道格拉斯先生?
Right, Mr. Douglas?
周二之前把正确的数字放在我的办公桌上
Have the final numbers on my desk by Tuesday.
就照你说的办 老板
If you say so, sir.
约瑟夫很棒 是不是?
Joseph's good,isn't he?
好吧 我要杀了你
Well,I'm going to kill you.
嘿 嘿 我只是觉得约瑟夫是喜欢搅和事情的那种人
Hey, hey, I just figured Joseph's the kind of guy who likes to mix it up.
你知道 进入状况 搅乱一池春水
You know, get in there, ruffle some feathers.
为什么呢?
Why?
听着 我很抱歉 但是 约瑟夫就是这样的人
Look,I'm sorry, but that's what Joseph does.
好吗?如果你想耍什么小聪明
Okay? If you try to pull something...
他会揭发你的
hell call you on it.
他会说 你想耍什么小聪明?
"What are you trying to pull?'he'll say.
噢 胶带
Ooh. Duct tape.
我是不是也应该带点东西来?
Was I supposed to bring something too?
这是给外面那对抓痒双胞胎的
This is for the scratchy twins out there.
我用胶带把烤箱手套黏在他们手上了
I taped oven mitts to their hands.
你还真严厉
You're strict.
是啊 这是为他们好
Yeah. well,it's for their own good.
你知道吗
You know, I like
我喜欢你很有效率地把胶带头这样折一下
the way you have efficiently folded this tab under.
要急用胶带时
See, in a tape emergency,
就可以省去好几秒宝贵的时间
you could shave valuable seconds off your time.
没错
Exactly.
天啊 我很喜欢我现在在你身边可以完全的神经质
God I love that I can be totally neurotic around you now.
跟我说实话
Tell me the truth.
你不觉得你更喜欢
Dont you like it better that
办公桌上的一切都是垂直摆放的吗?
everything on your desk is perpendicular?
如果不是正确的角度 那就是错误的角度
If it's not a right angle, it is a wrong angle.
非常好      谢谢
Very good.        Thank you.
你知道吗? 明天我要调整你的钟
You know what? Tomorrow, I'm gonna do your clocks.
你要怎么调整我的钟?
You're gonna do what to my clocks?
我要设成我的时间
I'm gonna set them to my time.
好吧 我困惑了
Well.I'm confused.
我以为我们的时间都一样呢
I thought we shared time.
没有 没有 你看 我把卧室里的钟调快了六分钟
No. no. See, in my bedroom I set my clock six minutes fast.
你想知道为什么吗?
You wanna know why?
因为卧室和厨房的时区有点不同?
Because it's in a slightly different time zone than the kitchen?
你知道吗?算了 我不要告诉你
You know what? Forget it.
不 来吧 来吧 告诉我
No, come on, come on, tell me.
不 你不明白      不 说吧
No, you dont understand.        No, come on.
你没有任何这些很可爱的小怪癖
No, you don't have any of these cute obsessive things.
不对 才不是呢 不是这样的
No.that's not true. That is not true.
哦 是吗?      是啊
Oh, yeah?        Yeah.
好 给我讲一个你的怪癖
All right, well, tell me one of yours.
好吧
Okay.
我有个怪癖就是 我总是把我的运动袜...
One of my things is, I always separate my sweat socks...
和套装袜分开
from my dress socks.
是啊      如果它们混在一起呢?
Yeah.        What if they get mixed up?
天啊 我会...
Boy, I would just, uh...
我会抓狂的
I would freak out.
你才不会
You would not.
我不敢相信 我讨厌这样 你太正常了
I cant believe this. I hate this. You're too normal.
我不敢相信我的男友没有任何怪癖
I can't believe my boyfriend doesn't have a thing.
我的男朋友没有任何怪癖
My boyfrienddoesn't have a thing.
看 如果有人偷听到 我的名声就完了
See, if anyone overheard that, I didn't come off well there.
道格拉斯先生正在找你
Mr. Douglas is looking for you.
为什么道格拉斯先生要找我?
Why? Why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?
因为他强烈地怀疑 你的贷款项目搞砸了
Because he has a strong suspicion that you dropped the ball on the Lender project.
为什么呢?为什么他要怀疑?
Why? Why does he suspect that?
因为一开始 他以为是约瑟夫...
Because at first, he thought it was Joseph...
不过在问过约瑟夫之后 发现其实是你
but after he asked Joseph about it, turns out it was you.
无论如何 我只是觉得你应该知道      好了 够了
Anyway, I just thought you should know.        All right.That's it.
听着 乔伊...
Look, Joey...
对不起 我知道这是你一生最重要的角色
I'm sorry, I realize this is the role of a lifetime for you...
而且如果我可以开除约瑟夫的话,我会的
and if I could just fire Joseph, I would.
可惜的是那是不可能的
But unfortunately that's not possible.
所以我要把你们俩都炒了
So I'm gonna have to let both of you go.
你说什么呢? 大家都喜欢约瑟夫
What are you talking about? Everybody loves Joseph.
我不喜欢 我恨约瑟夫
I don't. I hate Joseph.
好吧 我认为他是一个拍马屁的烂人
Okay, I think he's a brown-nosing suck-up.
哦 是吗?
Oh, yeah?
你不能开除约瑟夫 你知道为什么吗?
Well, you can't fire Joseph. You know why?
他不在你的部门
He's not in your department.
好吧... 所以我不能解雇约瑟夫...
All right, okay.All right,so I can't fire Joseph...
不过我可以和他老婆上床
but, uh, I can sleep with his wife.
不 凯伦      是啊 凯伦
Not Karen.        Yeah, Karen.
我在考虑和她搞婚外情 哦 你知道吗?
I'm thinking about having an affair with her. Oh, you know what?
我刚跟她搞完
I just did.
你对我干了什么好事?
What the hell are you doing to me, man?
哦 不是我干的
Oh,it's not me.
是我的角色
It's my character
钱迪
Chandie.
是啊 这个流氓处理员 专门引诱同事的妻子...
Yeah, the rogue processor who seduces his coworkers' wives for sport...
然后第二天还在饮水机旁当笑话讲
and then laughs about it the next day at the water cooler.
事实上 她的内裤就在我的抽屉里
In fact I have her panties right there in my drawer.
真的?      不 疯子 她是虚构的!
Really?        No, freak show, she's fictional!
好啦!放轻松
Come on! Take it easy.
如果对你意义如此重大 我...我会去找别的工作
If it means that much to you, I'll, uh-I'll go find something else.
谢谢
Thank you.
只是...我会想念约瑟夫
It's just that I'm gonna miss Joseph.
我喜欢他 他的妻子
I liked him. His wife.
她很火辣
She was hot.
请把这些摘下来 我发誓 我不会抓的
Please take these off. I swear I won't scratch.
不行 对不起 亲爱的 摩妮卡的命令
No, sorry, hon.Monica's orders.
还真不容易
Well that wasn't easy.
好了 晚餐好了
Okay,dinner's on.
有一个桃子派在烤箱里保温
And there's a peach cobbler warming in the oven.
所以盘子会很烫 不过对你们来说应该不是问题
So the plate's gonna be hot. but that shouldn't be a problem for you.
好了 你们两位 再见了
All right, you kids. Bye, now.
再见      哦 快看
Bye.        Oh, look, look.
一场低预算的木偶戏
A low-budget puppet show.
真可惜 你看不到我比的中指
It's such a shame you can't see what finger I'm holding up.
好吧
All right.
葡萄酒?      请
Wine?        Please.
洒了一些出来      让我来
Oh. Spilled some.        l got it.
我必须告诉你 你今晚很漂亮
I must tell you, you look beautiful tonight.
什么?
What?
对不起
Sorry.
你看起来真漂亮
You look beautiful.
你知道吗?够了...
You know what?That's it.That's it.
噢 太棒了
Oh, yes.
很好
Good.
两位 你们...?
You guys, did you-?
摩妮卡 醒醒
Monica, wake up.
摩妮卡      什么事?
Monica.        What's up?
我想到了一个怪癖
I thought of a thing.
是吗?      是啊
Yeah?        Yeah.
我必须睡...必须 睡在床的这一侧
I have to sleep, have to, on this side of the bed.
不 亲爱的 你必须睡在床的那一侧...
No, honey. You have to sleep on this side of the bed...
是因为我必须睡在床的这一侧
because I have to sleep on this side of the bed.
还是我让你那样认为的
Or so I would have you believe.
不是 有什么大不了的 每个人都有睡某一侧的习惯
No. Big deal. So you have a side of the bed. Everybody has a side of the bed.
嘿 别这样 你还没有听我的理由呢
Hey, come on. You haven't heard my reason yet.
好吧 继续      好吧
All right, go on.        Okay.
我必须睡在西边
I have to sleep on the west side...
因为我是在加州长大的
?because I grew up in California...
否则...
and otherwise...
海洋就会在错的一边了
the ocean would be on the wrong side.
哦 我的天 你是一个怪胎      是啊
Oh, my God.You're a freak.        Yeah.
怎么样啊?
How about that?
雷恩 你要潜到哪里去?      我真的不能说
So, Ryan, where are you shipping off to?        I really can't say.
你们艇上有核武器吗?
So do you have any nuclear weapons onboard?
我不能说
I can't say.
那么 你可以透过潜望镜那种玩意儿看东西吗?
Well, do you get to look through one of those periscope thingies?
对不起 我不能说
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
哇 学习到潜艇的知识真不错
Wow it's neat learning about submarines.
我得走了 不然该错过班机了
I better get out of here. I'm gonna miss my flight.
好吧 我送你出去
Okay, I'll walk you out.
再见 雷恩      幸会了 保重
Bye, Ryan.        Pleasure. Take care.
那么你认为我们可以借一套那种制服吗?
So do you, uh, think we could get you one of those uniform things?
你喜欢 对吧?
You like that, do you?
哦 是的      让我打几通电话
Oh, yeah.       I'll make some calls.
好吧
Okay.
你能相信我们是这样度过这两星期的吗?
Can you believe that's how we spent our two weeks?
我们一件我计划的浪漫的事都没做
We didn't do the romantic things I'd planned...
像是在中央公园野餐 在中央咖啡厅喝咖啡
...like having a picnic in Central Park and, you know, a coffee at Central Perk.
噢 我们刚刚才喝过
Oh, I just got that.
计程车
Taxi.
再见了
Bye, you.
对不起 我们打烊...
I'm sorry,we're clo...
嘿 水手
Hey sailor.
这是你脑子里想的吗?
Is this what you had in mind?
没错
Ha ha.I'll say.
我明天出发
I'm shipping out tomorrow.
嗯 那么...
Well, then, uh...
我们最好好好利用今夜...
we better make this night count.
哦 等一下 我忘了关卡布其诺咖啡机
Oh, wait, I forgot to turn off the cappuccino machine.
起锚吧
Anchors aweigh.
哦 等等 我的钱包...
Oh, wait. My purse, my purse, my purse.
哦 你知道吗? 我忘了关洗手间的灯
Oh, you know what? I forgot to turn off the bathroom light.
好吧 我何不在楼上等你就好了
All right, why don't I just meet you upstairs?
亲爱的
Honey.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧